無聊的歌曲是 嘰嘰嘰
Boring song pi pi pi
每一天都快樂 嘰嘰嘰
Happy Everyday pi pi pi
嘰嘰嘰
pi pi pi
豬之歌是 吭吭吭
Song of the pig doi doi doi
每一天都快樂 吭吭吭
Happy everyday doi doi doi
吭吭吭
Doi doi doi
猴子的歌是 吱吱吱
Monkey's song ji ji ji
每一天都快樂 吱吱吱
Happy everyday ji ji ji
吱吱吱
Ji ji ji
河馬之歌是 烏拉拉
Hipo's Song wo la la
烏拉拉 烏拉拉
Wo la la wo la la
喂 停停停
Hey, cut, cut, cut.
又是烏拉拉錯了吧 烏拉拉
Wolala wrong again, wu lah lah
烏拉拉啊
Wu lah lah ah
以後你不要獨唱了
No more solo for you.
是
Yes
烏拉拉 烏啦啦啦
Wu lah lah lah ah, Wu lah lah lah ah
這怎麼都唱不明白啊
Howcome you just don't get it?
唱唱看啊
Try Sing again!
讓你唱一唱啊
Sing Again!
怎麼總是隨便更換內容啊
Why are you keep changing lyrics?
導演難道是官嗎
Is director a Jugde?
什麼
What?
之前不是說我很好的嗎
Few days ago you said I'm good.
不是說我聲音很清脆的嗎
Ain't you said my voice sounds good?
不會唱歌並不是犯罪啊
Can't sing is not a crime.
好啊 不幹了 不幹了
Alright, I quit
反正我也沒想永遠做下去
Anyway I don't intent to work for life.
趕緊把之前的工資清算給我吧
Pay me the rest of my wages
昨天導演沒在 飯錢是我交的
Director wasn't in yesterday and I paid for the meal.
一起清算給我吧
Pay me back all of it.
－音癡診所－
-Tone Deaf Clinic-
--飛天餅--
--Flying flat Cake--
喂
Hey
你怎麼總是貼在別人傳單上面啊
Why are you covering others flyers
把頭盔摘了 摘了
Take off your helmet.
頭盔 頭盔摘下來啊
Helmet, Helmet, Take off!
你幹什麼啊
What are you doing!
去哪裡啊
Where you going?
放開我
Don't touch me!
是女人啊
Is a woman.
是啊 我知道身為女人幹這種活很累很丟人
I know is embarrass and tiring for a woman to work this kind of job.
你喜歡吃生魚片嗎
Do you like Sashimi?
難怪就知道生吃
Only know eating raw
所有的一切都一樣 要知道用努力換取成果
Is logically, You need to work hard to get reward
知道了 知道了 對不起 行了吧
I know, I know, I'm sorry.
一副乞丐德行 還這麼拽
What a proud beggar.
什麼 乞丐
What? Beggar?
給我站住 站住
Hey, Stop, stop!
你給我站住
Stop there!
喂 你
Hey you!
被我抓住你就死定了
You're a dead meat
你給我站住
Stop there!
啊 該死的
Idoit!
你給我站住
Stop there!
--順姬家飛天餅--
--Shunji Homemade Flying Flat Cake--
我回來了
I'm home.
回來了啊
You're back
小姨 還沒好嗎
Is my order done yet?
嗯 馬上就飛去 稍等
Soon will fly there, wait a minute.
來 接住 OK
Alright, there! Ok!
那邊
There.
進球
Goal!
小姨 我們這的呢
How about ours?
馬上就去了
Here it comes!
啊 好燙 好燙
Ah is hot, is hot!
怎麼非得這時候出來啊
Why you have to comes out this time?
哎喲 上次燙的地方還沒有好呢
Ah the last time burned still not recover yet.
你到底為什麼這麼對我
Why you have to treat me this way?
我不是早就讓你去種頭髮了嗎
I have already told you to plant some hair.
哎喲 就因為是光頭才那麼燙
It won't be that hurt if there is hair.
全貼完了
All done.
200張嗎
200 Piece?
是300張
Is 300 piece.
怎麼才這點啊
Why so little?
那你先把之前借的錢還給我吧
Why not you return what you owe me previouly.
身為媽媽對唯一的女兒放高利貸 很好玩嗎
Do you think is funny? Giving loan
to your only daughter?
哎喲 無期限 無利息 那算什麼高利貸
Loan without interest and due date?
那叫做善事
That is charity.
誰讓你把好好的工作辭了啊
Why quit the last job?
我都說是導演太欺負人了啊
I've already said, director bully me.
媽媽 別這樣
Mom, please.
我今天真的有很重要的事
I really have a very important
event today
您能不能稍微再給一點啊
Please give me little bit more.
媽媽
Mom
真是
you...
知道了 臭丫頭
ok, ok
你這個小偷啊
You such a thief.
不准看
Don't look
哎喲
Oh!
媽呀  就給我剩一萬元
You left me with only 10,000 Won
小偷 喂 這是什麼啊
Thief! Hey, what is this?
禮物啊 媽媽不是說少一個脱鞋的嗎
Is a gift. You short of one slipper,right?
壞ㄚ頭
Bad girl
這是從哪裡拿來的啊
Where she get this from?
來人
Anyone?
嗯 歡迎
oh Welcome
大嬸 你有沒有見過頭盔啊 頭盔
Did you saw a helmet? Helmet?
什麼
What?
就是帶著頭盔 給你家貼廣告的打工妹
Girl that wears a helmet, sticking flyers for your shop.
哎喲 那個我們只負責給錢
Oh, I only responsible for paying them
打工妹是誰就不知道了
Who is that girl, I've no idea.
用專業用語就是外助
In professional term, they're helper.
這個臭丫頭到底跑哪去了
Where's that bitch.
大哥 我現在腦袋完全點著了
Bro, I'm in the mood now.
我們打敗天地喝杯酒吧
Let's drink. How's that.
這裡嗎 這裡是...
Here? Here is...
但是我今天是不是白白放棄了晚間生意啊
But that mean I'm giving up my night revenue
早知道營業好了
If I knew, I just operating normal.
我有好多同學的
I have a lot of school mates
都說了我今天會負責提高你的營業額了
I've already said, I'm responsible
for the volume of you business.
哎喲 夢到是挺大
Oh, you really dream big.
會有幾個人來見你這個消失了十年的朋友啊
Who will come to see a long
lost friend, like you.
來三四名也都是多的
If three to four of them are here, your're lucky.
不過我真的覺得你好神奇
But I think you are really amazing.
一年的話 你不是基本都忘記他長相了嗎
By right, for a year you already can't recalled his appreance.
你怎麼會依然喜歡他呢
Why you still miss him?
是很微妙
Is strange
但是呢 民秀的模樣 到現在也很清晰
But, his apperance still very clear to me.
怎麼樣 大家要不要去運動場跑兩圈啊
How is it? You guys want two round run on the field?
不要
No
快點唱啊
Sing, qiuck.
喂 我會一直給你打節拍
I will always give you the beat.
不管是什麼時候 你只要唱出來就行
I don't care when, all you need just sing.
2 2 3 4
漠不關心的眼神 不要忘記我
Those unconcern look, don't forget me.
你明亮的心 太過閃耀 我認可
Your bright & shining heart, I will...
不要試圖欺騙我
Don't try to deceive me...
就算你不說話
Even you don't speak
但是你看我的眼神
But the way you look at me
可以證明你喜歡我
can tell that you like me.
對我深陷 深陷 深深的陷入
Toward deep, deep, deep,deep inside me
老師
Teacher
明知道她不會唱歌
You knew she can't sing
你何必非得逼著她唱歌 讓她丟人啊
Why force her to sing and embarrass her.
是不是太過分了
This is too much.
安靜
Quiet
臭小子 你這是對老師反抗嗎
You stinky kid, are you against your teacher?
你給我出來
You get out.
搖起船槳 輕輕的
Rolling a boat, gently
姐姐 你還是去加入爬山隊吧
Sis, I think rock climbing is better for you.
這對健康有益
Is good for health.
合唱隊和你沒緣分啊
You have no luck in choir.
閉嘴
Shut up
媽媽 嚇死人了
Mom, you scares me.
都說讓你敲門了 真是的
Already said knock before you come in.
喂 敲什麼門啊 門不是開著嗎
Oh, Knock? Door is open.
不過你怎麼突然在唱歌
Why suddenly you start singing?
你要考音樂考試了嗎
Going to take music examinations.
She want to join the choir.
什麼
What?!!
被男人迷得昏頭轉向了
She's obsessed with a man.
臭小子 要你管
Stinky kid, mind your own business.
喂喂喂 等等
Hey, Hey, Hey, Wait!
哎喲 行了
Enough
怎麼這麼快
Why so fast?
我還能唱的
I could still sing.
你不知道嗎
You don't know?
難道只有我感覺到了嗎
Don't tell me I'm the only one feel it.
你的音聲帶很奇怪啊
Your vocal sounds so weird.
不是男生 也不是女生
Not male, not even female
請問 你會彈鋼琴嗎
Do you play piano?
什麼
What?
嗯 中學之前一直有學
When in high school,
I always play piano.
結束
Finish
彈的不錯啊
Not bad.
唱歌雖然有點不怎麼樣
Although singing not so good
但是伴奏也是重唱團員
But piano accompaniment is
also part of quartet members
不錯吧 前輩
Not bad. Senior.
我同意
I agree.
我也是
Me too.
好吧
Alright.
但是不要唱歌哦 不行哦
But please don't sing, ok
喂 集中一下
Hey, attention please!
今天大家都知道
As everyone know
来了一位新伴奏者，请给她鼓掌
there's a new accompanist. Let's
give her an applause.
還有要離開去日本的 我們永遠的伴奏者
And also, someone is leaving
to Japan, that is Our forever accompanist,
民秀的歡送會 鼓掌
Ming Soo's farewell applause.
辛苦了
We appreciate it.
好好好
Good
我們一起聽聽一直給我們伴奏的民秀的歌聲吧
Let hear our accompanist Min Soo sing.
大家鼓掌
Everyone applause.
樸民秀 樸民秀 樸民秀
Park Min Soo, Park Min Soo, Park Min Soo
這首歌其實是思念我媽媽的時候唱的歌
This song was sung when I miss my mom.
但是以後我也會唱這首歌思念著大家
But next time I will sing this
song when I miss all of you.
坐在花園裡
Sitting in the garden
看著花瓣
Looking at the petals
這美麗的光芒是從哪裡來的
Where is this beautiful light coming from
美麗的花啊 花啊
Beautiful flowers, flowers
等我很久了嗎
Waiting long time?
給你 这是樂譜
This music book is for you.
這是我們練習用的CD 還有累積的磁帶
This CD is used when practicing
and some cumulative tapes.
民秀
Min Soo
嗯
Hun
大概得多久
How long you gonna leave?
不知道 最起碼得五年吧
Not sure, at least 5 years.
是嗎
Really?
是要去日本嗎
Japan?
路上小心
You take care
喂 你也好好過
Ok, same to you.
也要在合唱隊繼續努力哦
and keep it up in the choir.
再見
Good bye
民秀
Min Soo
加油
Keep it up!
嗯 好 你也加油
Ok, you keep it up too
－我會愛你－
- I will love you-
好久不見了
Long time no see.
想死你了 朋友
Miss you so much, my friend
你怎麼才來啊
At last you're here
感覺不錯啊
You looks good.
看他連啤酒肚也沒有呢
his beer belly is gone
好久不見了 民秀
Long time no see, Min Soo
她是誰啊
Who is she?
不記得了嗎
You can't remember?
那個唱歌不好 只能伴奏的人
The one that can't sing, but only accompanist...
啊 羅東珠
Ah Da Dong Joo
哇 你變了好多啊 變漂亮了
Wow, You change a lot, you turn pretty.
哦 真的嗎 你也很帥
Really? You look handsome too.
是嗎
Really?
見到你很高興
Happy to see you.
很高興
Very happy.
過得好嗎
How is everything, Good?
嗯
Yeah
起來吧
Get up
哎喲 社長您的聲音很不錯啊
Wow you sing not bad.
真的真的嗎
Are you sure?
聲音很清脆 都能出專輯當歌手了
Sing so good that you can have your own album
媽呀 我經常聽這種話呢
Jesus chris, I heard that all the time.
是吧
oh yeah
所以再唱一下吧 把後面得呼吸拉長一點
You should continue, try Stretch longer at the end.
來 準備 開始
Come on, ready, go
媽呀 媽呀 不要這樣
Mom ah, mom ah, please stop that...
女人的心是稻穗
Woman's heart are like rice
你看 你看 這樣更好啊
You see, you see, is better this way.
真的 真的嗎
Really? Really?
你怎麼這麼會唱歌啊
You really know how to sing.
你过奖了
You flattering me
不過啊 那個我們桌上還剩下個餅
But, that flat cake on the table...
你能不能幫我保管到冰箱裡啊
can you help me to keep it in the fridge?
知道了 知道了
Understood
下次來的時候你教我唱顫音吧 行嗎
Next time, can you teach me to sing vibrato,ok?
那當然了 謝謝款待
No problem, Thank for your hospitality.
大姐 這個傢伙能不能也保管啊
Can you keep this also?
嗯 知道了 知道了
Oh sure, sure.
我會好好幫你保管的 別擔心
I'll keep it safe. Don't worry.
大姐的聲音真是會動搖人心啊
Your voice really could rock someone's heart.
我以後會經常來這裡的
I will come here more often.
走啦 別隨便耍酒瘋 真是的
Get out, you're drunk
那人怎麼回事啊
What happen to him?
是東珠今天提供了場所哦
Is Dong Joo provide this place.
哦 是嗎
oh really?
謝謝了 東珠
Thanks Dong Joo.
喝一杯吧
Let's drink
嗯
oh
那麼今天我們合唱隊最後一首歌
So today, our last song
最後的歌手
The last singer
各位 你們快樂嗎
Are you guys happy?!
是
Yeah
今天在場唯一的小姐
Today, our only lady here.
美貌的性感女
Beautiful and sexy.
請她唱首歌吧
Let's Welcome her to sing
文寶拉小姐
Miss Man Bo-ra
唱歌文根兒 美貌無雙文寶拉
Let's sing, beautiful Man Bo ra
坐在花園裡
Sitting in the garden.
看看花瓣
Looking at the petals
這美麗的光芒是從哪來的
Where is this beautiful light coming from
美麗的花啊 花啊
Beautiful flowers, flowers
這麼好的日子裡
Such a good day
東珠啊 她唱歌真好聽
Dong Joo, she sing so good.
什麼
What?
不准作夢
Dream on
什麼
What?
你以為我沒看到嗎
You thought I did not see it?
你在說什麼啊
What are you talking about?
你那個笑容 勾引男人時候用的
That smile, When you used to seduce a man.
別隨便诬蔑我
Don't slandering me.
不是嗎
Aren't you?
我堅持了這麼久 就為了搶朋友的暗戀對象啊
I insisted for so long just to grab a friend's crush?
才不是呢 不是
Of course not.
那倒是
Yeah, right.
別亂關心一些沒用的
Stop thinking of nonsense.
是吧 是吧
Alright, alright,
我們寶拉才不會這樣
Bo Ra won't do such thing
走開啦
Get lost.
你 絕對不准變心哦
You, do not cease to be faithful, ok?
這純潔的心要一直保持到底哦
You must remain faithful till the end
都說讓你走開了
I've alreay said, get lost.
原來是邀請函啊
So this is an invitation letter
你這傢伙十幾年來一直沒有消息
You brat, there is no news from you for 10 years.
真是太没禮貌了
That's really rude.
很抱歉啊
So sorry.
但是我們好久沒有對過嘴了
Has been long time we never sing together.
對什麼嘴啊
Sing together?
喂喂 我是說給我婚禮唱祝福歌啊
I mean sing a blessing Song for my wedding.
知道了吧
Get it?
你們一定要練習好唷
You guys have to practice more ok?
特別是羅東珠 你
Especially, Da Dong Joo
要好好表現
Give a good performance.
敢給我丟臉就等著瞧
If you embarrass me, you will see.
喂 別擔心 東珠只要張口不出聲就行
Hey, Don't worry, Dong joo just lip sync will do.
有什麼難的
How hard it could be.
喂 不要看扁我
Hey, don't look down on me.
我哪裡需要只張口不出聲啊
I don't need lip sync.
我現在唱歌很好聽的 我不是以前那個羅東珠了
I sing quite well now, I'm not that last time Dong Joo
哇 真的嗎
Wow really?
是啊 我是聲藝演員 我的聲音很清脆的
Yup, I'm a Soundcraft actress and voice is crystal clear.
哇 真的嗎
Wow are you sure?
那東珠要不要一個獨唱啊
Then Dong Joo, do you want a solo?
獨唱嗎
Solo?
是啊 趁這個機會好好聽羅東珠的歌吧
Well,we'll take this opportunity to listen Da Dong Joo's Singing.
嗯 好吧 獨唱就獨唱吧
Oh, Alright, I'll solo.
那有什麼難的
What so hard about that.
來 東珠 為了羅東珠乾一杯吧
Come Dong Joo. Let's cheers for Da Dong Joo.
乾杯
Cheers!
為慶祝東珠的獨唱 乾杯
Cheers for Dong Joo's solo
東珠 開車沒事嗎
Dong Joo, can you drive?
嗯 沒關係 我沒喝多少
Is ok, I did not drink a lot.
已經醒酒了 沒關係
I'm sober, is alright.
要不要我陪你啊
Do you need me to accompany you?
什麼
What?
至少有人陪你说话没那么闷
At least someone can talk to
you and you won't be bore.
嗯 好啊
oh ok.
等一下哦
Wait a minute.
東珠 小心開車哦
Dong Joo, Drive carefully.
什麼 哦
What? OK
明明感冒了 剛吃藥 怎麼還喝那麼多酒啊
Just had her cold medicine and why drink so much?
民秀 你離她遠一點 會被傳染的
Min Soo, stay a distance from her, you may get infected.
寶拉現在還在感冒呢
Bo ra is still having cold.
沒關係
Is alright.
不過東珠
But Dong Joo...
嗯
Hun
我沒想到寶拉唱那首歌唱的那麼好聽啊
I never expected that Bo Ra
could sing that song so well.
聲音真是與生俱來的啊
Her voice is really innate.
是啊
Yeah
東珠
Dong Joo
嗯
Hun
你把電話號告訴我吧
Can I have the phone number?
電話號
Phone number?
我的嗎 為什麼
Mine? Why?
要電話號幹嘛
Why need my phone number?
我是說寶拉的電話號
I'm saying Bo Ra's phone number.
寶拉啊 啊
Bo Ra...ah ah
誰啊
Who's that?
喂
Hello
你好 寶拉 我是樸民秀
Hi, Bo Ra, I'm Park Min Soo.
羅東珠高中同學
Dong Joo's High school mate
你昨天還好吧
Are you ok yesterday?
喂 你能聽見嗎
Hello, can you hear me?
是我失禮了嗎
Am I impolite?
我問東珠要的電話號
I got you number from Dong Joo.
嗯 是啊 是我 東珠
Oh, yes, is me, Dong Joo.
我好像把我的電話號告訴你了
I think I have given you my number.
什麼
What?
啊 是嗎
Oh really?
不過你找寶拉有什麼事嗎
Anything important looking for Bo Ra?
啊 不是 沒什麼特別的
Ah, no, nothing special.
昨天謝謝你了 託你的福還和朋友們見了面
Thanks for yesterday. If is not because of you,
I won't get to see all my friends.
嗯 好
OK
有機會再聚在一起吧
Meet again if we have chance.
嗯 再見 嗯
Good bye
真是要瘋掉了
really going mad
咦 對了
Oh yeah
早知道不說要獨唱了
Shoudn't have said solo
獨唱 獨唱
Solo, Solo
音癡診所
Tone Deaf Clinic
啊 等等
Ah WAit
喂 失業者 失業者
Oh Unemployed, Unemployed
不是呢 是大嬸
Nope, is Aunt.
才不是呢 是在家發霉的霉女
Of course not, is those homely moldy girl.
喂 看她的臉 後腦勺都老了
Her face and behind her head looks old.
就是啊
Right
估計不是“走出去”
I guess she's not "walking out"
難道是“鄉巴佬”的志願者嗎
Don't tell me she's a Country Bumpkin volunteer.
--音癡診所 超越想像的學生特價！--
-- Tone deaf Clinic, Student price--
你好 我是聲音好的博士 我是聲一清
Hello, I'm Professor Good voice. My name is Sounds Clear.
我以为你到了才打电话上来 没想到这么久才来
I thought you call from downstair,
who knows you took so long.
啊 我是去換了身衣服才來这
Ah I changed my clothes then came here.
好熱 好熱
Really hot
哦 同光高啊
Tong Guang High School
是復學生嗎
You're students returning from leave?
只是在校學生
current student
哦 在校生啊
Ah current student
唱歌不難 誰都能唱好歌
Is not hard to sing, everyone can sing well.
唱歌的一半是自信心
Is about confidence.
還有剩下的一半 也是自信心
And what you need is confidence too.
莫拉納諱特說過這麼一句話
Morane said before
音樂不會大過我 歌曲不會大過我
Music & song won't be bigger than me.
我是1米75 我的歌聲才1米65
I'm 1.75 and my singing only 1.65
誰更高 我更高
Who's taller, I'm taller
誰做的 是我做的
Who done that, I done that
用什麼做出來的 是用自信心做出來的
What created that, confidence created that.
你現在開始也能成為名歌手
From now on, you could be a singer
跟著我來做吧
Follow me
brrrrrr
跟著我來做吧 跟著做
Follow me
噴口水也沒關係一起來
Is ok to spit.
brrrrr say---
sayga---ya---
大聲喊 喊 ya
Shout louder ya...
有診斷了
Diagnosed
一個月4次 只要365天
4 times a month. Only need 365 days.
你就會被你的朋友們稱之為歌手
All your friends will call you Singer.
12個月你可以去參加super star 成為第一
You can take part in Super Star and
becomes winner in 12 months.
24個月可以去 《我是歌手》名譽畢業
24 months later, you can take part in the
《I'm A Singer》then you're honorary graduate.
36個月就輪到你來教我
Is your turn to teach me after 36 months.
啊 不過我很著急
But I'm urgent
能不能快點學習啊
Can I start as soon as possible?
那麼我會給你找個指導老師
Then I'll find you an Instructor.
課堂可以是一週四次
Can be four times a week.
當然授課費也會增加
But tuition fee will increase too.
是多少
How much?
一週4次 一月30萬
A week 4 times, a month 30,000 Won
我聽說有學生半價才來的呢
I heard there's 50% discount for student.
反正是學生 打五折15萬
For student discount 50% 15,000Won
那我就來一週4次吧
Then I'll take up that per week 4 times.
那就立刻登記吧
Then registered immediately.
或者帶你媽媽來也行
Or you want to bring your mom along?
不用 我媽媽 已經去世了
No need, my mom already passed away.
真是要瘋掉了
Really go mad.
喂 你還有臉跟我要錢啊
You still have the cheek to ask me for money.
媽媽 我愛你 我愛你
Mom I love you, I love you
愛你 愛你 愛你
I love you, I love you, I love you
哎喲 起來起來吧
Aiyo, get up, get up.
你又又又要用到哪裡 用到哪裡
Why you need the money?
你猜猜看
You guess...
喂 求你找個工作談談戀愛吧
I beg you, go find a job and find a love one.
媽媽最想要的是什麼
What mom really wants.
你難道還不知道嗎 當然是讓你結婚啊
You still don't know? Of course,
is to let you get married.
我打算滿足你的願望
I intend to fulfill your wish
真的嗎
Really?
你是哪個高中的
You are that high school student?
啊是同光高中嗎
Tong Guang High School?
是
Yes
是修行評價練習嗎
Are you practice for evaluation exercises
你們班是愛你羅 還是稻田
You class is Ai niLo or Ricefield
什麼
What?
啊 是在花園裡
Ah is at the Garden
什麼
What?
換音樂老師了嗎
Changed music teacher?
反正今天不能教你唱歌哦
Anyway I can't teach you singing today.
暫時練習呼吸法和發聲
Temporary just exercises on breathing and vocal
什麼
What?
不過我真的很急 那種東西能不能pass掉啊
Is quite urgent, can I skip that?
我們身體裡發出的聲音可以分為鼻音和頭音
Sound can be divided into nasal sound and head sound.
鼻音是從鼻子裡發出的聲音
Nasal sound is the sound from the nose
那麼頭音是從哪裡發出的聲音呢
Then where is the head sound from?
很聰明 是從腦袋裡發出的聲音
Clever, is the sound from the head.
那麼先練習腹呼吸
Then will starts from abdominal breathing
腹呼吸是拉屎時候用力一樣的呼吸
Abdominal breathing is the same force when shiting
我們拉尿的時候瞬間發力的那個重點
The moment when we force to shit, that's the focal point
要記住那個重點才可以
Remember that focal point
發聲的時候也一樣
Is the same when vocalize.
像拉屎時候一樣用力 像是要把便排到體外一樣
using the same force when shiting,
is like forcing shit out.
方向雖然是相反
Although it's at the opposite direction
但是想要排出去的東西會一樣的順暢
But whatever you have force out,
you'll feel clear and coherent
好累啊
Really tired
來 那麼起來練習一下吧
Come on, let's practice.
起來吧
Get up
來 在肚子裡吸滿呼吸 慢慢吹
Inhale into your belly slowly blow out
來 這種方式 跟我做
This way, follow me.
快來
Come on
不對不對
Wrong, wrong
你的肚子沒有凸出來啊
Your stomach need to protrude out.
要讓肚子凸出來 像是青蛙一樣
stomach protrude out like a frog
青蛙肚子 好好看我
Frog stomach. Ok, look at me.
哎喲 真是的
Oh Damn
對不起了
Sorry
那個 稍微休息一下吧
Then, rest for a while
去幫我倒杯水吧
Get me a glass of water
喂喂 喂
Hey,hey,hey
真是髒死了
So disgusting.
脖子太疼了我今天就先走了
My neck is too pain so I'll call it a day.
剩下的課讓院長幫你上吧
The rest of the lesson, Professor will take over.
老師 你怎麼了
How are you teacher.
沒關係 沒關係 別碰我脖子 別碰
No problem, I'm ok, Don't touch
my neck, Don't touch
脖子怎麼回事啊
What happen to your neck?
關你們什麼事
Hey mind your own business
該死
Damn
今天的課就到此結束了
Is end of today's class
啊 課結束之後又畢業生歡送會
After end of lesson will be graduate farewell party
請大家留下來吃肉吧
Hope everyone could stay for BBQ
東珠學生也是
Dong joo, you too.
吃牛肉
Have some beef.
來 再次真心祝賀今天畢業的畢業生們
Come on, let's congratulate today's graduated student.
也希望後輩們也繼繼努力
Also hope those juniors will put in more efforts
完美的脫離音癡境界
And break away from tone deaf
啊 今天的乾杯主題是像家族一樣
Ah today's cheers topic is "Like a family"
是要院生們象家人一樣相處的意思
It means all students will get along like family
我說家
I'll say "We are"
你們就說人一樣 就可以了
You guys say "family" that's all
來 舉杯
Come on, let's toast.
祝賀各位 家
Congratulations to all " We Are"
族一樣
Family
從江原道來回跑參加補習班 確實有效果
From Gangwon Road run here and back
to attend tution class really got effect
但是每個章節都需要準備兩首歌呢
But required to prepare two song for every chapter
因為別人總是會搶走我的歌
Because others will always steal my song
弄的我心臟撲通撲通 緊張個不停的感覺
Making my heart beats fast and feeling nervous.
我也是
Me too.
我們要不重新開始學習吧
Why don't we start learning again.
所以我有屬於我自己的Rap啊
That's why I have my own rap.
--靠近 盡情的大聲尖叫!--
--Get near, Enjoy and scream--
怎麼樣
How is it?
這麼晚了啊 我得先回去了 孩子還等我呢
Is late I have to leave. My son's still waiting for me.
恭喜你了 真心恭喜你
Congratulation!
我先走了
I'll leave first.
再見
Bye
老師 你好
Hello, teacher
嗯 你們好 好啊
Hi everybody
沈老師 不是說來不了了嗎
Teacher, I thought you said can't make it.
聚餐怎麼能少了我呢 我連石膏都解了
How can I miss a dinner party,
I even have my neck cast removed.
哎喲 好口渴
AIyo so thirsty.
院長 我先走了
Professor, I'm leaving.
我媽媽會在家等我的
My mom will wait for me to go home.
東珠學生 你不是說你媽媽去世了嗎
Dong Joo, I thought you said
your mother has passed away.
喂 學生怎麼能這樣
Hey, how can a student be like that.
什麼
What?
要理直氣壯地喝 理直氣壯
Wanna drink, be bold and straight.
這算什麼啊 偷偷喝
Why have to hide?
喝酒要從一開始學好了才行 喝吧
To drink have to learn from the beginning. Let's drink.
老師
Teacher
怎麼了
What?
我們呢
How about us?
你們是中學生啊
You guys are high school student.
老師 我和她是留級了一年的
Teacher, I and her retained one year
切 這個姐姐是高3
This sister is in year 3
但是看看 好好看 仔細看
But take a look, see carefully,a closer look
像不像留級2年了似的 或者是3年
Does she look like retain for 2 years or 3 years?
我也不管了 吃吧 吃
I don't bother, let's eat.
我去趟洗手間
I'm going to the toilet.
老師老師
Teacher, teacher
喂 你怎麼來這了
Hey, why you are here?
托老師的福 我考上了這次的海選
Have to thank you, I passed the audition.
我明天去M國
Going M Guo tomorrow.
M國 真的嗎
M Guo, are you sure?
來來 坐下吧
Come over here and sit down.
真是太恭喜你了
Congratulation to you.
你怎麼去的啊
How you get in?
是靠實力去的
By my ability
他是在這裡學習才成這個水平的嗎
Is he learn from here to reach this level?
是哥哥好不好
Could you address him as senior?
那麼小怎麼這麼沒禮貌啊
So young and no manners.
他聽了該多不高興啊
He will be upset if he heard you.
我看起來真的像是高中生嗎
Do I really look like a high school student?
身為學生怎麼能這麼說啊
How could you says such thing?
你媽媽該為你操心啊 不是高三嗎
Your mom should be worry about you.
Aren't you high school 3rd year?
是高一嗎
Or first year?
不是不是 是高三 在校生
No, no. Is 3rd year.
這是宮社長
This is Deputy Chief.
有很多錢
Very rich
像他這樣的人是與生俱來迷人的重低音
People like him are born with a charming bass vioce
可以看做是特有的體聲
Can be treated as special voice
但是唱歌的時候總是會结巴
But always stammered when singing
结 结巴的毛病需要改一改
This st- st-stammer problem needs to be alter.
太结巴了
Too stammer.
出聲啊 出聲
Sing out, Sing out.
挺直腰板
Straighten your back
那大嬸性格很好 很外向
That aunt has a good personality, very outgoing.
但是一拿麥克風就會抖的要命
But once touches the mic she will start trembling.
根本出不了聲
Can't sing out at all.
停 停
Stop! Stop!
Bravo Bravo太棒了 太棒
Bravo, Bravo, Fantastic, Wonderful!
我教了十年
I've taught for 10 years
你是我見過的最棒的音癡 節奏癡
You are the most tone deaf and rhythm retard.
你得花不少時間啊
You have to take quite some time.
大概得多久
Roughly how long?
多久嗎
How long?
你是高三嗎
High school 3 now?
什麼 是
Why? Yes.
就當你運氣好30歲左右能結婚吧
Consider you lucky enough by 30 year old got married
還運氣好的生下了女兒
and very lucky give birth to a daughter.
等到那個女兒好好長大成為高三為止
Wait until your daughter grow up and in high school 3
什麼
What?
那之前 都不知道你能不能好好唱首歌啊
until then, no idea you could sing well or not.
什麼
What?
把飛機降落的聲音改成歌曲 反而會更簡單啊
By changing a plane crash sound
into song will be better for you
怎麼有這種人渣啊
What an idiot.
你多大了
Then how old was that?
31歲
31 years old
你剛剛對我平輩相稱了嗎
You've just address me as same generation?
是啊 平輩想成了
Yeah, so what.
你这個乞丐德行
Act like a beggar.
你 乞丐喂
You! Beggar hey!
怎麼能這麼沒禮貌
How dare you be so rude.
怎麼能這麼隨便對學生說話啊
How can he talk to a student in such manner.
口臭加狐臭 我再也忍不住了
Bad breath, body odor, I can't endure anymore.
最起碼沈老師有穿鞋啊 這已經很不錯了
Consider not bad, at least
your teacher still wear a shoe.
脫鞋的話 所有的學生估計都會逃走的
If is slippers, all students would have gone
但是他實力確實不錯 稍微忍一忍 加油
But he's quite competent.
Just endure and keep it up.
大哥 不行啊
Bro, no way!
用教學的方式改變歌聲也是有限度的
There's a limit on using teaching
method to change the way she sing.
哪有不可救藥的音癡啊
There's no hopeless tone deaf.
連餅家的大嬸也能改啊
Even that aunt from the flat cake
shop can also be change.
那種人肯定會到時候帶著媽媽來要退錢的
End of the day she sure bring
along her mom and ask for refund
喂 臭小子
Hey, idiot!
突然喊什麼啊
Why suddenly shout?
她沒有媽媽
She don't have a mother.
沒有媽媽不是還有爸爸嗎
No mother, but still have father, right?
媽媽沒在 怎麼可能有爸爸啊
No mother, how could she has father?
學音樂的人 心胸怎麼這麼乾枯啊
Being a musician, why is you heart so dry?
像是沙漠似的
Like desert.
我說 你帶她去吃點好吃的 好好勸勸她吧
Bring her out for dinner and try to persuade.
怎麼給這麼多啊
Why so much?
哪多了 才一萬而已
Not a lot, just 10,000Won
是十萬啊
Is 100,000Won.
我給錯了
My mistake.
給錯了 錯了
My mistake, mistake!
謝謝
Thank You
喂喂喂
Hey, hey, hey
啊 是誰把錢印得都差不多啊
Who the hell printed those notes so similar.
該死的強盜
Damn robber.
真想揍死他
I'll kill him.
我有一個好奇的事
I'm curious about something.
你為什麼想學唱歌
Why you want to learn singing.
不想跟我說話嗎
Don't feel like telling me?
好吧 吃飯 吃飯
Alright, eat, eat.
雖然不知道是什麼原因
Although I don't know what's the reason.
但是光把歌唱好並不能解決一切的事
But can't solve any problem by singing well
够了
Enough!
啊 燙死了
Hot
你趕緊教教我吧
我會一天10小時24小時的練習
You just make it fast and start teach me.
I will use 10 hours or 24 hours to practice.
是嗎
Really?
你不是說你想學速成的嗎
I thought you want to take up the crash course?
我有個作業
I have an assignment.
--歌--
--Song--
媽媽 媽媽
Mom! Mom!
媽媽 姐姐 姐姐她
Mom! Sister, Sister, She...
姐姐她去見男人了
Sister was seeing a man.
這穿著校服
And she's wearing school uniform.
校...
School...
金師傅
Mr. Kim
我都說了第二個棒子往前放一點
I've said, shift the second pole forward a bit!
我都說多少次了 要對準這個線
I've said many times, align this.
啊 還不如閉眼睛幹活了 笨死了
Might as well close your eyes and work, Stupid.
真是要瘋掉了
I'm going crazy.
請問
Excuse me.
怎麼了 小姐
Yes? lady...
你是來打工的嗎
You came here to work?
跟我說吧 我是這裡的負責人
I'm the in-charge here.
You can speak to me.
不是 不是的
No, no
請問這裡的舞台導演在哪裡
May I know where is the theatre director?
你都來這麼遠了我卻只能請你吃個飯啊
You came from so far and I only can treat you a meal
對不起 不過你應該也很忙的吧
I'm sorry but you should also busy, right?
我一點也不忙
No, not at all.
民秀
Min Soo
嗯
Hun
我 最近在學唱歌
I'm learning singing recently.
而且還是在非常專業的教育機關裡
In a very professional educational institutions
哦 是嗎
Oh really?
老師說我是時隔十年聽到的最棒的聲音
And the instructor said I have the best voice.
真的嗎
Really?
嗯
un
對了 祝福歌準備得怎麼樣
Oh yeah, how's the blessing song?
你不是說要獨唱嗎
I thought you said you want solo.
嗯 有再好好選擇
un I'm preparing
歌曲定好了嗎
Decide any song yet?
在花園裡
In the garden
什麼
Hun?
我喜歡那首歌
I love that song.
你不是也很喜歡的嗎
You love it too, right?
大叔 大叔
Uncle, uncle
沒有錘子啊 錘子
There's no hammer.
沒有錘子嗎
No hammer?
老師
Teacher
你在幹嘛
What are you doing?
哎喲 你坐下啦
Aiyo, sit down.
你在幹嘛啊幹嘛呢
What are you doing?
嗯 現在終於能活了
hm...finally able to live
該死 你在幹嘛
Damn what you trying to do?
这是禮物 身上有味的時候噴一噴吧
This a gift. When there's body odor, just spray.
嗯 謝謝了
Oh, thank you.
喂 趕緊準備上課吧
Hey, quicky, ready for class.
肚子用力 再大聲
More power, louder.
再大聲 再大聲
More louder, more louder
可以了 稍微休息下吧
Ok, take a rest.
這個給你喝
This for you.
我都不喜欢咖啡
Since when I like coffee.
那個人又來了 是不是變態啊
Is him again. That pervert.
就是啊 怎麼一直偷拍啊
Yeah...why keep taking picture.
他是不是偷拍校服的人啊
Pervert school uniform photographer
是啊
Yeah..
去看看 看看
Go take a look.
喂 我也穿校服了啊
Hey I'm wearing uniform too.
那也去調查一下吧
We have to investigate.
哎喲 幹什麼啊
Ah What??
讓你偷拍 讓你偷拍
Let you shoot, let you shoot
媽媽 姐姐
Mom, Sis
喂喂喂 你們在幹嘛
Hey hey hey, what you guys doing?
老師 他是變態
Teacher! His a pervert.
是專門追穿校服女生的慣犯
His the recidivist who shoot on girl school student.
這種傢伙得揍死才對
This kind of fellow should die.
不是
No
變態嗎
Pervert?
不是的
I'm not.
慣犯嗎
Recidivist?
不是的
I'm not.
看你臉上肥嘟嘟的肉
Look at your fat face.
你們幹嘛啊
What you guys doing?
誰讓你出來做壞事的
Who let you out commit crime.
真是 我不知道你們為什麼這麼對我
Really...I don't know why you guys doing this to me.
但是我的腿不能动了 幫我叫下119吧
But my leg can't move now, please call ambulance.
求你們了
I begging you guys.
你好 伯母
Good day, madam.
姐姐 你在家啊
Sister, you're home?
姐姐嗎
Sister?
哎呦 真爽口
Ah...really nice
頭髮散下來 看起來很成熟啊
You look mature with the hair down.
你到底多大了
How old are you actually?
別管別人的事了
Stop being busy body.
什麼啊
What?
你都畢業大學了啊
You're already gratuated from college.
你到底多大了
How old are you actaully.
不會是為了受學生折扣才穿著校服了吧
Don't tell me you wear an uniforn for the discount.
那個 我有點隱情
That...I've some hidden reason.
我以後會告訴你的 院長那邊請你幫忙保密
I'll let you know next time, but please
keep this secret from professor.
真是個神神秘秘的女人啊
Really a secretive woman.
哦 竟然還有人家裡有這東西
Oh...you have such thing at home.
沒有就隨便找個東西代替不就行了
You can just replace by anything.
竟然還買回來了
You actually bought this back.
到底是單純還是傻啊
Are you simple or stupid.
什麼
what?
祝福歌嗎
Blessing song?
而且還是獨唱
And is solo?
是不是清醒著啊
Are you sober?
你覺得這像話嗎
Don't you think is ridiculous.
都說有隱情了 你幫我個忙吧
Already said there's hidden reason.
Help me please.
好吧 就當我能幫上忙 讓你唱祝福歌吧
Alright. Let's treat it I can help you.
那麼最起碼得把婚禮推遲一年才行
But at least postpone the wedding by a year.
不對不對 大概得兩年
No no, around 2 years.
真是的
Stop it!
别瞪我了
Stop staring at me.
行了 行了 試試看不就好了
OK, ok, I'll try.
不行
Yes
我能做到
I can do it.
年輕人 你很辛苦啊
Young lady, life's hard.
您先去吧
You go first.
这样能測試你的節拍感吧
This will test on your Sense of rhythm
不是那樣 要在花瓣的時候稍微降音
Not like that, you have to gradually decrease your tone.
再来一次
Repeat
行了 行了 休息下吧
Alright, alright, rest a while.
從哪裡來的 那個部分重來
Repeat from the middle part.
你是不是火星人啊
Are you from mars?
就當是呼唤着遠處的男友吧
Treat it as calling your distant boyfriend.
不對不對 再來了
No, no, again.
喂喂喂 還會有這麼好的日子嗎 會嗎
Hey hey hey, are you having good time?
花瓣啊的時候用力
Middle part use more strength.
很好
Very good.
是啊 就睡一個小時吧
Yes, just sleep for one hour.
这是什麼味道啊
What's that smell?
你還能睡得著啊 睡得著啊
You still got the mood to sleep?
沒剩多少時間了 快起來啊
We don't have much time, get up.
不小心睡著了
Just fall asleep.
D-感情豐富點
D- More feeling
在腦海裡抓節奏
Grap the rhythm in your mind
對了很好
Right, very good.
肚子用點裡
Use some abdomen power.
很好
Vey good
Good
是不是還可以
Is it alright?
哇 成功了 成功了
Wow I did it, I did it.
喂 你進步不少了哦
Un...you improve a lot.
謝謝
Thank You.
喂 我本來就教的很不錯哦
Un proved that I taught well.
再來一次吧
Let's try again.
-再來嗎
-好
_Try again
-Ok
喂從高音開始來吧 高音部分
Hey start from the high tone
哎喲 腰疼啊
Ar... backache
喂 你怎麼了
Hey, what happen to you.
眼睛裡進東西了
Got something in my eye.
進東西了嗎
Something went in?
喂 那麼柔可不行啊
Hey, don't rub it.
喂 我吹吹看吧
I'll try blow it.
睜開眼睛 呼 呼 呼
Open your eye.
行了夠了
Ok enough.
行了嗎
Ok?
好了嗎
很好 很好
Is good, is good.
啊 好像太勉強了 全身酸痛啊
Ah I forced too hard. Whole body aching.
不過你怎麼都不讓我睡一覺啊
And you don't even let me sleep awhile.
昨晚他们到底做什麼了啊 真是的
What they really did yesterday night. Damn.
該死
Damn!
真心祝賀兩位結婚
Sincerely congratulate both of you.
在這神聖的教堂裡的新娘新郎
The bride and groom In this holy church
還有各位賀客們
And all guests
在此代替兩家父母 感謝大家
Meanwhile, I represent both parents to thank everyone.
的士 的士
Taxi...taxi
真是的 路太堵了
Damn, so heavy traffic.
大叔 我還是先下吧
Uncle, I'll alight here.
給你
There.
喂
Hey.
該死
Damn.
嗯 好
Er...good
先給賀客們說一聲抱歉
First, I like to apologise to all guests
下個獨唱部份因為有问题
There is some problem in next solo part.
嗯是解決了隱情 已經到達現場了
Problem solved, she has arrived.
喂 失業者
Ah Unemployed.
冰凍
Frozen.
喂
Hey.
你是蛇女嗎
Are you snake woman?
蛇女不是長得很漂亮嗎
I thought snake woman were beautiful.
明明是個老狐狸
She's an old vixen Obviously.
你竟敢勾引我們老師
How dare you seduced my teacher.
穿著校服裝作是高中生
Wearing an uniform pretending
to be a high school student.
真是太讓人無語了
We really out of words.
喂 還有你
Hey... and
大晚上的和我們老師做什麼了
What you did with our teacher that night?
你們在幹嘛 老師嗎
What you guys doing? Teacher?
你裝什麼不知道啊 你这個狐狸
You this vixen. Pretending
you didn't know anything?
失败者
looser
你們在說什麼
What you just said?
说你失败者 失败
Says you looser, looser
別拿學唱歌為藉口勾引我們老師
Don't use singing lesson as an
excuse to seduced our teacher.
還是去找別人吧
Go find somebody else.
小心我讓你照遺照啊
Be careful, I'll give you a funerary.
喂
Arr...!!!
你們今天來的正好一起上吧
You guys come at the right time, lets fight.
喂
Er...!!
你們死定了
You guys are dead meat.
用這個遮著 把手拿下來吧
Use this to cover.
Put down your hand.
別在遮著你的脸
Stop covering your face
真是適合你啊
Really suits you.
身份證號
Identity number.
什麼
What?
你說什麼
What you said?
你都28歲了 竟然還和小孩子打架
You already 28 years old still fight with kids.
28歲
28 years old?
哪 吃吧 派出所紀念
There...eat! Police station souvenir
你是逗我笑 還是找死啊
You trying to make me laugh
or looking for trouble
廢話真多
Stop talking nonsense
那個很燙啊
Is hot!
燙死了
Really hot.
我感覺要死了
I feel like going to die.
呼吸不暢 真奇怪
So strange, can't breath well.
我今天唱歌完全失敗了
I failed on today's solo
但是我要重新學歌 然後在民秀面前好好唱一次
But I'll start learn again and show off to Min Soo
會讓民秀喜歡上的
I'll make Min Soo likes me.
大嬸 再來一隻生章魚吧
Aunt! One more raw octopus.
分不開啊
Can't separate them.
大嬸
Aunt
還是放著吧 放著
Better to leave it, just leave it.
給它們一個能活下去的機會
Give them a chance to live.
誰啊 是誰
Who, who's that.
是誰點 趕緊取消訂單
who's order? Cancel the order at once.
它活得多辛苦啊
They're so suffering.
沒看見它們是相愛的嗎
Can't you see they're in love?
相愛並不是件容易的事啊
To be in love is not an easy thing.
是誰點的啊 是誰
Who ordered this? Who?
大嬸
Aunt
取消章魚
Cancel the raw octopus.
大叔帥呆了
Uncle, so handsome.
相信我 坐下吧 這家真的很不錯
Trust me, sit down. This shop is really good.
有那麼好吃嗎
Really that delicious?
這家的章魚最棒的 是招牌菜啊
This shop's raw octopus the best.
Is their signature dishe.
那嚐嚐看吧
Should try.
大嬸 這邊來一瓶燒酒 一個章魚
Aunt! One bottle of wine and raw octopus.
啊 都說不行了
Ah already said no.
喂喂喂
Hey hey hey
都說不行了
I say no!
你還是讓他們相愛吧
Please let them in love.
他們兩個是為了殺死彼此才這麼吸著的
Both of them are trying to kill each
other then suck together.
沒看見在互相撕咬嗎
can't you see they bite each other?
看不見 看不見 不看了
Can't see it, can't see it, can't see it.
喂 你哭了嗎 哭了嗎
Hey are you crying?
唉呦 耍酒瘋就是頭痛啊
She's drunk, really giving me headache.
走吧 走 清醒一點 走
Lets go, go, be sober, go.
哎喲髒死了
Er!!! Damn dirty!
小姐
Miss
安靜點 真是太頭疼了
Please be quiet. Really headache.
喂 之後怎麼走
Hey after this where is it.
什麼
What?
怎麼走啊
Which way?
年糕餅 年糕餅
New year Flat cake, new year flat cake
什麼狗屁年糕餅啊
What the hell new year flat cake.
你都吐了 還想吃什麼啊
You vomited and still what else you wanna eat
年糕餅 年糕餅 年糕餅
New year flat cake, new year flat cake
好吧 那家的年糕餅確實好吃
Alright, honestly that flat cake shop is really good.
但是你現在不是吃年糕餅的情況啊
But you're not in the state of mind to eat flat cake now.
年糕餅 年糕餅
New year flat cake, new year flat cake
你真是太讓我頭痛了
You really giving me headache
年糕餅 年糕餅
New year flat cake, new year flat cake
這麼大年紀 就不要裝可愛了
Already that old then stop acting cute.
年糕餅
New year flat cake
真是個瘋女人
Crazy woman
喂 你這個樣子 小心我把你綁在樹上
Hey, do that again I'll tide you up to the tree.
喂 你
Hey you.
社長 情況有點不好啊
Chief bad situation now
媽媽 我回來了
Mom I'm back
媽媽嗎
Mom?
喂 你竟敢灌醉我女兒
Hey how dare you making my daughter drunk
真是的 那大嬸手勁兒真大
Damn, That aunt really strong
這到底是什麼回事啊
What actually going on?
不是高中生 還是年糕餅家的女兒
Not a high school student and is flat cake shop's daughter.
那麼 那麼 頭盔
Then... then... helmet
喂
Hey
起來 起來起來
Get up, Get up, get up.
哎喲 酒味
Smell of liquor.
把這個喝了
Drink this.
你最近到底怎麼了
What happen to you recently.
我怎麼了
What happen to me?
突然喝醉酒不說
Let don't talk about tonight incident
突然學歌是為什麼 那個男的又是誰
Suddenly you went to learnt singing
and who's that guy.
誰啊 我們老師嗎
Who? Our teacher?
你喜歡那傢伙嗎
You like that fellow?
我瘋了嗎
Am I crazy?
喂 你知道那傢伙是個多麼奇怪的人嗎
Hey do you know that fellow is a very weird person?
之前經常來我店喝酒
Previously, he often came to my shop and drink.
每次喝酒還總是用代金卷來喝
Always use a vouchers for drink.
那個人有點髒而已 但不是壞人
He just dirty but not a bad person.
喂 那傢伙是不是要灌醉你 然後意圖不軌啊
Hey is that fellow try to make you
drunk and do something to you?
是不是差點要出事了啊
Are you nearly in trouble?
都說不是了 你出去啦
I said no. Get out.
推什麼推
What's that pushing about?
哎喲
Damn
姐姐 寶拉姐姐來了
Sis, Bo Ra is here.
寶拉啊
Bo Ra?
你怎麼來了
Why are you here?
晚安
Good Night.
你有什麼事嗎
What is it?
我今天喝了好多酒哦
I drink a lot today.
我是想東珠了 才來的
I miss Dong Joo, that's why I came.
你脫了絲襪再睡吧
Take off your stockings then sleep.
臭丫頭
Bitch
我見過的男人 你知道有多少嗎
How many men I've seen do you know?
你都不知道 我怎麼會知道啊
You don't know, how would I know.
我怎麼樣
How am I?
什麼
What?
戀愛的時候
When in love...
怎麼說呢
How should I put it.
一直扮的很性感
Have to act sexy all the time.
--樸民秀--
--Park Min Soo--
今天是做夢一樣
Is like a dream today.
能重新聽到寶拉的歌聲 讓我非常高興
Could hear Bo Ra sing again making me so happy.
星期五在“芭蕾”劇場見吧
See you this Friday at the Ballet Theater.
媽呀
My god.
竟然把手機扔進了冰箱
Throwing handphone into the fridge?
東珠
Dong Joo
咦 寶拉
Oh Bo Ra
喂 你們兩個怎麼
Hey both of you...
啊 是我有一張多餘的票
I have extra ticket
所以邀請寶拉小姐來的
so I invited Miss Bo Ra here.
你自己來的嗎
You came alone?
啊 不是 和媽媽來的
No, I came with my mom.
哦 伯母啊
Where's your mom?
在哪裡啊 我打聲招呼吧
I like to say hello to her.
還沒有到嗎
Not here yet?
嗯 媽媽好像來晚了
She will be late.
你們先進去吧
You guys go in first.
嗯 好吧
Ok.
我先進去了
I'll go in first.
嗯 今天預約客人突然爆滿 沒時間啊
Suddenly full house and a lot of
guest booking today... I can't leave.
我叫明石去了 你們好好看吧
I get your brother to meet you.
You guys enjoy.
媽媽 客人難道比我還重要嗎
Are those guests more important than me?
嗯 很重要
OH very important.
媽媽 喂 媽媽
Mom! Hey mom!
你怎麼现在才來啊
Now then you're here.
拉上去 拉上去
Pull up, pull up
你是我朋友吗
Are you my frined?
我都知道了
I already know everything.
我上次看了你的短信
I read you phone message that day.
應該是有隱情吧
There should be a hidden reason, right?
我相信你
I believed you
那個
That...
要不一起去吃個飯吧
why don't we have dinner together.
吃飯 好啊
Dinner? Ok.
-不用了 -不用
-No - No
我有點累了
I'm a bit tired.
東珠 你開車來的嗎
Dong Joo, you drove here?
嗯
Yes
送我回去吧
Send me home.
我送你回去吧
I'll send you home.
我坐東珠的車回去就好
I'll take Dong Joo's car.
走吧
Lets go
再見
Bye
嗯 再見
un...bye
你不能自己搭公车回出吗
Can't you just take a bus home?
不就是搭個便車嗎 怎麼這麼多廢話啊
Just a free ride why you have to talk so much.
是你弟弟把票給了我 我才去的
Your brother gave me the ticket, that's why I went.
而且也只是坐在了那個位置而已
And is just sitting on that seat.
不過今天的演出真的好棒
But today's performance really great.
知道了 你給我安靜點
I know... Shut up
失敗了就重新开始吧
Try again after failure.
不是說要重新練歌的嗎
I thought you said practice sing all over again?
明天早上去發聲練習
Lets go for vocal training tomorrow morning.
9点正到學院前面集合
Assemble 9 am sharp in front of the school.
再大聲點
More louder.
聲音要唱響桶的內部 再大聲點
Sing inside the barrel, more louder.
老師
Teacher.
幹嗎
Why?
能不能休息一會兒啊
Can't we take a break?
累了嗎
Tired?
休息十分鐘
Rest 10 minutes.
石頭剪刀布
scissors, paper, stone.
怎麼自己在這坐著啊
Why sit here alone?
啊 養活兩個孩子弄的我體力不夠啊
To feed two children making me physically weak.
哇 你 看起來不像是孩子的媽媽啊
Wow, you don't look like having two kids.
哦 我28歲了
I'm already 28 years old.
什么...那你不是和我同歲吗
WHat? We are same age?
我以為你真的是高中生呢
I thought you're really a high school student.
真是童顏啊 你得謝謝你媽媽
You have to thanks your mom, you have a baby face.
我可是長得很老哦 我很討厭我媽媽
I hate my mom because I look old.
一起練習吧
Lets practice together.
不想練了
Don't feel like practice.
越來越覺得累了
Feeling more and more tired.
雖然不知道发生什么事
Although I do not know what happened.
不過一定要加油哦
But make sure to keep it up.
我也在堅持呢
I'm still persist.
來 大家一起去聽聽自己的聲音吧
Come on everyone, lets hear your own voice.
你去吧
You go ahead.
一起去吧
Lets come together.
一起去啦
Come on.
我的寶貝兒子
My lovely son.
媽媽真的想給你们唱催眠曲
Mom really wanted to sing to you a lullaby
但是 媽媽一开始唱
But once I start sing.
大家就會笑我
Everyone will laugh at me.
所以媽媽害羞唱不出來啊
Thats why mom feel embarrass
and unable to carry on.
再等等我吧 媽媽能做到的
Give me sometime, mom will make it.
為什麼每个星期都要去練歌廳2到3次呢
Why every week have to go karaoke 2 to 3 times?
聲音不好聽的話 大家也不會期待啊
Everyone wouldn't expect me to sing, if I don't sing good.
我都要瘋掉了
I'm going mad.
要是這種聲的話 也就不會有人叫我唱歌了
No one would want me sing if I sing really bad.
為什麼選歌手非得看臉蛋啊
Why choosing a singers have to go for the looks first?
就是
Yeah!
你們歌唱得也不好啊
You guys don't sing good too.
啊 煩死了
Boring...
我呢
And me...
不是為了讓大家看才學習唱歌的
I don't intent to learn singing just to let everyone see.
我呢
And me...
對於脫離音癡之類, 沒有一點期望
I don't have any any expectation on getting rid of tone deaf.
只是 想在喜歡的人面前
Just wanted to show the one I love...
想要好好的唱一首歌而已
I can sing well.
不是因為缺乏自信
I'm not lack of confidence.
我真的只想好好唱一首歌
I just want to sing a song properly.
東珠 羅東珠
Dong Joo! Da Dong Joo!
來來來
Come on, come on, come on.
怎麼樣 喊了一下 覺得舒服多了吧
How is it after the shout? Feels better?
是
Yes.
我們也趁這個機會 在別人面前表演一下吧
Let us take this opportunity to perform to others.
什麼 表演嗎
What? Perform?
老師 真的表演嗎
Teacher, are you serious?
小事而已 試試看不就行了
Is a small matter, just give it a try that all.
把自己喜歡的人全部邀請來吧
Invite all the people you like.
怎麼辦 怎麼辦
What should we do? What should we do?
還有公演場所就定在我之前打工過的酒吧
We'll perform at the pub that I work prevously
怎麼辦 怎麼辦 太期待了
What should we do? What should we do? Really look forward to.
喂 可以嗎
Hey, is it ok?
怎麼不回答啊
Why don't you answer?
哎喲真是的
Oh dear.
這樣已經很幸運了
Is consider very fortunate.
怎麼辦啊 不過你也不能這樣啊
What to do now? But you just can't do that too.
你們就算這樣也帮不了
Even you did this, it won't help.
我絕對不會原諒你們
I definitely won't forgive you guys.
還有我打不打我老婆 離不離婚
And whether I hit my wife or to divorce or not...
和你們有什麼關係
what got to do with you guys?
快點滾啊 滾
get lost, get out!
不是 不是說要唱歌嗎 滾
Want to sing, right? Get out!
大叔 你先喝下飲料
Uncle, have some soft drink first.
先喝杯飲料 降降火氣吧 大叔
Uncle. Have some drink, cool down.
喝不了, 走吧
Unable to drink, please go.
沒看見這颈部铸嗎
Can't you see this neck cast?
從上面
From the top
哎喲
Er...
趕緊滾啊
Get out immediately!
再怎麼樣也不行啊 你怎麼能揍老公啊
No matter what just can't do that,
how could you beat up your husband.
你知道被揍的老公有多麼悲哀
Do you know how depress is your
husband being beaten by you?
特戰士
S.W.A.T team
李英愛小姐是特戰士下士出身嗎
Miss Lee, you are a Corporal from the SWAT team?
是
Yes
看看 看看
Let see, let see
跆拳道公認3段 特戰士
taekwondo known 3rd dan, SWAT
那你也不能揍你老公啊
That doesn't mean you could beat up your husband.
警察同志
Sir...
我一直瞞著這些事
I've been Concealed this matter...
一輩子都是被老公揍著活著的
All long while I've been beaten by my husband for life.
我今天 真的是第一次打他啊
Today was really my first time.
我還以為你天天去哪裡了
I'm still thinking where you go everyday.
你到底在想什么啊
What the hell were you thinking?
有時間唱歌
You got the time to sing?
你還不如教育孩子 收拾家務了
You might as well educate our
kids and clean the house.
最近沒被我打 是不是覺得皮癢了啊
Long time never get beaten by me is it?
嗯 嗯 哎喲
Hun...hun..er...
該死 吵死了
Idiot, bloody noisey.
你的廢話太多了
You talking too much rubbish.
喂 你知道姐姐為什麼一直忍著你嗎
Hey do you know why your "Sister" keep enduring you?
姐姐嗎
Sister?
我是你姐姐啊 我比你大一歲
I'm your sister! I'm older than you a year.
你被我打的話會死掉的
You won't be alive if I beat you up.
但是我再也忍不住了
But I can't endure anymore.
你得死一次試試才行
You have to die one time then you will know.
喂 想被我揍一晚上試試嗎
wanna try get wreck by me for a night?
喜歡被揍嗎
You like being beaten up?
哎呦 你这個老婆子是不是瘋了
Er...is this wife turn crazy?
呀
Ahhh...
辛苦你了
You've had a long day.
不過有點過分了
But a bit too much.
抱歉 讓大家擔心了
Sorry to make everyone worried
抱歉什麼啊
What's there to say sorry.
要不是他太過分, 你也不會那麼做啊
You won't do that if he's not pushing his luck.
他們就知道站在男人那邊說話
They always stand at the man's side of view.
不是 我只是說暴力是不太好的而已
No, I mean is no good to be violent.
這樣已經很幸運了
This way is consider lucky.
你老公好像也不怎麼生氣了
Your husband don't seem to be angry anymore.
快去醫院看看吧
Go visit him now
好 謝謝你們 再見了
Ok, thanks, bye.
-再見 -嗯
-Bye - un
--不賣活章魚--
--Not selling live octopus--
世界上沒有能隱瞞到底的事
You can't hide something forever in this world.
唱歌雖然很好
Although singing is good...
但是不想被別人搶走那個男人的話
But if you don't want anybody to snatch away your man...
就直接告白吧
then tell him straight.
親口對他說的話 不是會有個結果嗎
You'll have your answer if you tell in front of him.
走到底才會知道不會有回頭路
You will know when you go to the end,
and there is no turning back.
我上次也是因為收到女朋友的結婚請帖
Me too because of receiving a wedding invitation ...
在酒吧钢管那邊耍瘋
from my girlfriend and gone mad in the pub pole.
不小心掉下來 才打的石膏
Not careful fell down and have that neck cast.
你第一次見到我的時候
Your first time seeing me
就是因為那件事才弄成那個德行的
That's what happen.
所以現在反而慶幸再也不用回頭去看她了
That is why I'm glad instate and never think of her again.
啊 真是要瘋掉了
Ah... really hard.
有個非常絕妙的方法
There's a very wonderful way.
很奏效的 很適合
Sure works, very suitable.
但是身為院長 不太好開口說
But not so good for me to speak out as a principle.
院長大人
Principle, sir.
做!
Do it!
沈勇唱歌真的很好聽
Swen Yong's singing really great.
在這個歌聲裡添加東珠小姐的聲音
In this song, add in Dong Joo's voice.
好聽吧 是不是很好聽
Is it nice?
哇 怎麼做到的
Oh...how you do that?
只要把口音對好了就行 假唱
Just get your mouth right that all. Lip sync.
假唱 假唱
Lip sync, lip sync.
要對沈勇保密哦
Keep it a secret from Swen Yong.
大哥
Big bro.
一起去吃飯吧
Lets go for supper.
晚上怎麼吃飯啊 這麼晚了吃什麼啊
Is so late at night, where and what you wanna eat?
別嚇唬人
don't bluff people.
你怎麼了
What happen to you?
這麼晚了還怎麼吃飯啊
Is so late what there to eat!
東珠
Dong Joo
哎喲 抱歉 等我我很久了吧
So sorry, keep you waiting.
沒有沒有 我沒睡著
No no, I didn't sleep.
沒事吧
Are you ok?
嗯
Mm
這個
This...
這是什麼
What is this?
邀請函
An invitation card.
我的演唱會
My concert.
演唱會嗎
Concert?
是參加的一個組織開的演唱會
That organization I joined, holds this concert.
哦
Oh
你能來嗎
Can you come?
嗯
Um
真的嗎
Really?
嗯
Um
謝謝
Thank you.
真的很好聽
Really so nice.
你來找這個嗎
Looking for this?
還是放棄吧 要不就用你的聲音去唱
Why don't you give up or else use your own voice.
這算什麼啊
What is this?
給我
Give me.
你想用這個去參加演唱會嗎
You wanna use this for the concert?
把你的真實的模樣表演給他看吧
Use the really you.
除了這以為沒別的方法 你知道的
Other than this, there is not other way. You should know.
就算節拍和音調完全正確也並不能證明它就是歌
Even the beat are right doesn't mean is a song.
要把唱歌的人的真心投入到歌裡
Use the really emotion and apply to the song...
才能把它稱之為歌
Then that is called a song.
你算什麼
Who are you?
你有什麼資格對我指手畫腳
You don't have the right to comment me.
那麼喜歡就直接跟他告白啊
So like him then tell him.
別逞強要唱歌
Don't overexert wanting to sing.
把所有學員當成傻子來耍
You are treating all participants as a fool.
你是想說這次表演是為了我才開的嗎
Are you saying this concert organised because of me?
你不會是喜歡我吧
Don't tell me, you liked me.
那就說出來啊
Then say out.
你不是讓我說出來的嗎
Aren't you want me to say out?
說啊
Say
大家好 我是Dr.聲
音癡診所的院長 聲一清
Hi everybody, I'm Dr. tone deaf clinic's principle.
見到大家很高興
Very happy to see everyone!
今天來了很多人
Today came a lot of people.
今天在場的各位比我想像中的更有人性啊
Can't imagine everyone here today
got more humane than I thought.
史蒂芬言德說過這麼一句話
stephen yandle said...
缺點有時會成為自身最大的優點
Sometime disadvantages may turn into your own greatest advantages
當然也要伴隨著血汗努力
Of course it accompany with hard work.
今天到場的各位
Everyone here today...
都是吧自己的缺點轉化為最大優點的人
All are people that turning disadvantages to advantages.
首先從李英愛的表演開始吧
First of all, we start from Miss Lee's performce.
沒關係 沒關係
Is alright, is alright...
沒關係 沒關係 沒關係
Is alright, is alright, is alright
別哭了 再唱就好
Don't cry, sing again will be alright.
別哭了 再唱一次 沒關係
Don't cry, sing again, is alright.
沒關係
Is alright.
太棒了 太棒了
Very good! Very good!
恭喜 唱的真不錯
congratulation, you all sing really not bad.
這次音癡演唱會 拿去出專輯吧
This time tone deaf concert can have own album.
不行啊
Still not yet.
不是唱的很好嗎
I thought sing not bad?
沒想到真不错
Can't imagine, really not bad.
這種時候大家都會讓一讓哦
This situation everyone will give way.
去見見家人吧 來這邊
Go see your family...over here.
辛苦了 辛苦了
Thanks, thanks.
真是太讓我感動了 你唱的太好了
I feel so touch, you sing so good.
我唱得不怎麼好
I sing not so good.
沒有 唱的很好 看起來很好啊
No, is really good. Look at it very good.
謝謝
Thank you.
我們要不要一起吃晚飯啊
Do you wanna go for supper?
什麼
What?
好
OK
走吧
Lets go
東珠 坐這邊吧
Dong Joo, sit here.
嗯
Um
吃點什麼呢
What should we eat?
還是直接說出去吧
Is better to say it out.
說出去的話 不是會有個結果嗎
Say out will have answer, right?
民秀
Min Soo
嗯
Un
你知道我畢業專業是日文課嗎
Do you know I gratuated in Japanese
我每年都去日本旅行一次
I went Japan everytime once in a year.
上大學之後開始每年都去
I Went there every year after University.
東珠 我
Dong Joo, I...
我只是說我的事而已
I just said my own thing.
東京 沖繩 北海道 本州
Tokyo, Okinawa, Hokkaido, Honshu
摸索著那些道
combed through those streets.
我彷徨了十年
I wandering for 10 years
期盼會在路上偶然遇見你 或者見你一面
Expect to meet you accidentally
on the street or just see you.
我也想
I also thought that...
在你面前
In front of you...
好好得唱一首歌
to sing a song well.
像寶拉一樣
Just like BO Ra.
民秀
Min Soo
我的心 你不能理解嗎
What I'm thinking, you don't get it?
東珠
Dong Joo.
我
I...
對你
Towards you
這邊
Here.
東珠 我們好不容易才交往的
Dong Joo, is not easy for us to get together.
希望你能祝福我們
Hope that you could bless us.
東珠
Dong Joo.
因為你才弄成這樣的
Because of you everything mess up.
是你讓我全部說的 是你讓我走到底的
You want me to say everything,
you want me to go to the end.
你明明什麼都不知道 還指揮我
You actually don't know anything,
yet commanded me.
因為你 我再也沒臉見民秀了
Because of you, I don't know how to face Min Soo anymore.
你知道嗎
Do you know...
因為你 如果不是你的話
Because of you.
都怪你 都怪你
Is you, is you.
為什麼怪我 為什麼是我的錯
Why blame me, why my fault?
你今天唱歌唱得很棒
Today you sing very well.
你今天很漂亮
Today you were so pretty.
羅東珠 羅東珠
Da Dong Joo, Da Dong Joo.
喂 羅東珠
Hey Da Dong Joo
東珠 羅東珠
Dong Joo, Da Dong Joo
不要跟著我
stop following me.
跟我談談吧
Talk to me.
-不准跟著我 -啊
-Don't follow me -AH
喂 羅東珠
Hey Da Dong Joo
你這個笨蛋女人
Stupid woman.
1個月後
One Month Later
哎喲 你怎麼穿這種鞋啊
Why are you wearing this kind of shoe?
太高了
Is too high.
這樣才漂亮啊
This one more pretty.
讓我看看
Let me see.
喂 很好 快去吧 別遲到
Very good, quick, go, don't be late.
我走了
Bye.
喂 你要好好表現 不要亂發脾氣啊
Do your best perform well, do not often lose your temper.
加油
Keep it up.
回去吧
Go back in.
去吧
Go
唉呦 導演 導演
Oh director, director.
什麼啊 你不是辭職不幹了嗎
Why? I thought you have already resigned?
上次我真的真的做錯了
I'm really so wrong that time.
把舌頭伸出來說話吧
Stick out you tongue and speak.
別說什麼錯不錯的 反正以後也不用見面了
Who's wrong I don't wanna know.
Don't want to see you again.
我有很好的反省 還花錢去練習唱歌了呢
I felt remorse and I took up singing lesson too.
你聽聽看吧
Give me a chance.
烏拉拉的歌曲是
Wulala is the song of
烏拉拉烏拉 烏拉拉烏拉
Wu lala wula wulala wula
怎麼樣 是不是好一點了
How is it? Is it better?
反正你也沒有找到替補啊
Anyway you haven't found any substitute yet.
我得進去了
I have to go in.
導演 導演
Director, director!
喂 5分鐘後進來吧
5 minutes later come in.
不是說導演不是官嗎 還飯費
I thought you said director is not
a judge? And meals expenses?
你敢再來那種態度試試
Don't you dare try your bad attitude toward me again.
你當導演是什麼人啊
What kind of person you think a director is?
我做錯了 導演 我再也不這樣了
Is my fault. Director, I won't do it again.
看羅東珠小姐確實很深深的反省的份上
Miss Da Dong Joo, give you a chance since you repented
教訓就不用了
No need to teach you a lesson.
從上次烏拉拉那個錄音開始重新錄吧
Start record from that wu lala all over again.
知道了
OK.
1月民秀出國 今日民秀歡送會
Min Soo going abroad in January.
Today is Min Soo's farewell dinner.
不參人員請提前聯繫
Please contact early if can't make it.
乾杯
Cheers!
東珠 快來啊
Dong Joo, quick, come in.
坐吧 坐吧
Sit, Sit.
喂 東珠 小可愛
Hey, Dong Joo, cuite.
服務員來個杯子吧
Waiter! One glass please!
好像變漂亮了
Getting prettier now.
嗯 是漂亮了
Yeah really.
開車來的嗎
Drove here?
嗯 不過寶拉怎麼沒在啊
Un, but why Bo Ra not here?
你不知道嗎
You didn't know?
他們分手了
They broke up.
喂喂 喝吧 喝吧
Oh...lets drink...lets drink.
女人又不是只有寶拉一個
Bo Ra is not the only woman.
是啊 有紫色（寶拉的諧音）
Yup, There's purple (Bo Ra's Homophonic)
也有粉色 也有藍色
And pink, and blue.
喝吧 喝吧
Drink, drink.
民秀
Min Soo.
嗯
Un
為什麼啊
Why?
每次和我見面 她總是會想到你
She always think of you, everytime we meet.
所以覺得心裡難受了
Thats why she feels sad.
估計是沒有緣分吧
I guess we're fated can't be together.
餅還沒好嗎
Is the flat cake ready?
好 馬上就飛過去了
Ok will fly there soon.
哎喲
AHH!!
抱歉 抱歉
So sorry, so sorry.
我馬上就幫你拿過來
I'll bring to very soon.
哎喲就因為你没控制火喉才飛不起來啊
AHH!! because of you never control the
fire, thats why it can't fly.
這麼烤的話只會考糊外邊 裡邊都是生的
This way the outer part is over cook
and the inner still not cook.
知道嗎 這個和戀愛差不多
Understand? This one and lover almost the same.
戀愛嗎
Lover?
嗯 用溫火 先烤熟裡邊
Un, use warm fire to cook the inner.
覺得裡邊烤熟了之後
Inner is cooked then...
那時候在用大火把外邊烤一層
use big fire to cook the outer.
哎喲 就你這麼烤是談不好戀愛的
Ah...the way you cook, you won't
have a good relationship.
媽媽就是用這個手藝勾引了你爸爸啊
This is the skill that your mom
use to seduced your father.
嗯 這次很好
Un this time is good.
嗯 對了
Un correct.
輕點放啊
Put down softly.
您好
Hello.
哎喲 你還活著啊 好久不見了
Oh you still alive. Long time no see.
可以用代金券吧 社長
Chief, Can I use voucher?
真是厚臉皮 怎麼就知道用代金卷啊
Always use voucher, really thick skin.
開玩笑的開玩笑
I'm Kidding, kidding.
你當我是天天白天喝酒耍酒瘋的人嗎
You thought I'm a everyday drunken person?
是不是就算了
Doesn't matter.
不過你的脖子怎麼了
But what happen to your neck?
這是上次你把我
Last time you...
算了 不說了
Forget it...
跟我談談吧
Can we talk?
我這週日開演唱會
I'm having a concert this Sunday.
演唱會嗎
Concert?
嗯
Un
這個不是你的演唱會啊
This is not your concert.
哦 不是我單獨演唱會
Oh is not a solo concert.
我是去白頭山的演唱會當客人去的
I'm the special guest of this concert.
反正恭喜你了
Anyway congratulation to you.
謝謝
Thank you
對了
Oh yeah
這個
This one
這是什麼
what is this?
是紀念品
is a Souvenir
紀念品嗎
Souvenir?
我走了
Have to go back.
啊 我只在舞台上唱一首歌
I will only sing one song that day.
來晚了就聽不到了哦
If your're late you won't get to hear it.
明白了嗎
Understand?
我走了
Bye.
怎麼都不回答啊
Why don't answer me?
燈光先抓準中間 中間
Lighting on the center, Center.
在這邊拍一個人 拍穩一點
Shot a man here, a stable shot.
民秀
Min Soo.
東珠
Dong Joo.
是6點的飛機吧
6 o'clock flight?
還沒有遲到
Still not late.
再見了
Bye.
寶拉
Bo Ra.
在唱我的歌之前
Before singing my song...
先給前輩歌手來一場歡送的歌
let the senior singer give us a farewell song
來 各位 請掌聲鼓勵
Come on everyone lets applause.
這個
This.
是紀念品
Is a souvenir.
小姐 你沒事吧
Miss, Are you alright?
嗯 是不是看起來很不正常
un do I look insane?
雖然不知道是什麼事
Although I didn't know what happen.
但是我很羨慕小姐啊
But I admire you.
什麼
What?
有一個能讓你微笑的人多好啊
Is good to have a person that can make you smile.
那是福氣 也是幸福
That's a blessing, also a happiness.
我一輩子最大的願望就是讓別人微笑
In my lifetime, my greatest wish is to make others smile.
我真的不搞笑
I'm not joking.
不管講多麼搞笑的事
No matter how funny it is.
只要由我說出口 就不會好笑
From my mouth, will turn not funny.
嗯 怎麼了
Why?
姐姐 你在哪裡
Sis, where are you?
快到家了 怎麼了
Reaching home soon, why?
嗯 知道了 你等著
Un, ok, you wait.
什麼
What?
謝謝
Thank you
前面 摩托車 摩托車
Front bike, bike!
謝謝
Thank you
喂喂 你夠了沒啊
Hey are you enough?
呀呀 你是不是瘋了
Ah!! Are you crazy?
啊 我還活著 還活著
I'm still alive. still alive.
喂喂喂 你想死嗎
Hey You wanna die?
結束
End
真的嗎 真的嗎 真的嗎
Really? Really? Really?
喂 羅東珠 不是讓你準時到的嗎
Hey Da Dong Joo, have I told you not to be late?
你知道在埸的各位因為你听我唱了多少便吗
Do you know how many time everyone here have
to hear me sing over and over again because of you?
反正 這是最先想給你唱的歌
Anyway, this is the first song I wanna sing to you.
好好聽著羅東珠
Listen carefully,Da Dong Joo
always you sleep in my heart
forever you are in my life
我唯一的人
You're my only one
只有你
Only you
always i looking to your eyes
你的微笑過於燦爛
Your smile is so glorious.
讓我雙眼迷茫的你
You making my eyes hazy
我深愛著你
I love you deeply
-我的心臟要爆發了似的跳動 -上去吧
-My heart beating so hard -Go up
上舞台 上舞台 上舞台
Go up the stage, Go up the stage, Go up the stage.
是我姐姐
Is my sister.
真的嗎
Really?
Day by day, 夢想著你
Day by day, dream of you.
只會看到你一個
Only able to see you.
每一天都很幸福
Being happiness everyday.
be my girl請再我身邊
Be my girl, please by my side.
抓緊我的手 my love love love
Hold my hand, my love love love
always you sleep in my heart
forever you are in my life
我唯一的人
You're my only one
只有你
Only you
always i looking to your eyes
你的微笑過於燦爛
Your smile is so glorious.
讓我雙眼迷茫的你
You making my eyes hazy.
我深愛著你
I love you deeply.
always living in my heart
我想要告白
I like to fess up.
我唯一的人
You're my only one
只有你
Only you
always i looking to your eyes
我的心臟要停止了
My heart going to stop.
偷走我的人
You steal me away.
我深愛著你
I love you deeply.
親嘴 親嘴 親嘴
Kiss, Kiss, Kiss
不是這樣的
Is not like that.
不愧是羅東珠
Indeed is Da Dong Joo